James Capadocia

3218 W. Olive Ave Unit 3B Chicago, IL 60659

(847) 730-7599

iames.capadocia@gmail.com

Proficient In:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Client/Server Side APIs
- MySql

Summary

I intend to show the skills and achievements I have acquired over the past years of working experience and show that I am capable of performing honestly and diligently as a Front End Web Developer. Through the years of work in Sales & Servicing, along with my education in Coding & Full Stack Web Development, I have acquired the skillsets to understand how to communicate with customers/clients and bring to life what may start as a simple vision, to reality. While in this position, I am excited to continue to adapt to new technologies introduced into the space to further increase my skillsets and master my craft.

Experience

Digital Team Associate Banker BMO Harris Bank - Buffalo Grove, IL/Remote — 2017-Current

- Top Table Winner for fiscal year 2020
 - --> Top performer from each department in the North America Contact Center
- Consistently ranked top 3 on the Digital Team for efficiency in customer servicing each calendar month --> Based on average customers serviced per hour and personal NPS (Net Promoter Score)

Sales Account Executive SurePayroll (a Paychex Company) Glenview, IL — 2015-2016

- 3 time President's Dinner attendee for Q2, Q3, and Q4 (2015) attained by being at or above 110% of designated "blended" quarterly quota
- 1 of 2 "Rookie Account Executives" to earn a spot to Paychex's "Conference" event for fiscal year 2015
- Consistently achieved 100% or above in each quarterly quota category
- --> new units and revenue generated
- Elected to take part in the Sales Team Advisory Committee to be a voice of needs or concerns for the SurePayroll sales team

Retail Sales Lead T-Mobile Deerfield, IL — 2013-2015

- Promoted to Retail Sales Lead position for the store within two years of employment
- Winner's Circle Award recipient for Q1, Q2, & Q3 (2014)
- --> Top 5% of all sales representatives in the nation Achieved top performer consistently in monthly market "Rep Ranker" for the Chicago North Suburbs Market
- Exceeding monthly sales goals including sales in new accounts and add-ons to existing accounts
- Developing and leading a sales team to ensure store success and customer satisfaction

Other Qualifications

- Strong communication skills with customers/clients/prospects
- Proficient in time management and creating work schedules for myself to ensure work is completed in a timely and accurate fashion
- Experienced in data entry using Microsoft Excel

Education

NorthWestern University (July 2021-January 2022)

Full Stack Web Development Certificate